#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/prangyaparamita-behera-903aa576 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Technical Recruiting Screening Resumes Screening

## Prangya Paramita Behera

HR Recruiter at Microsoft India (R and D) Pvt Ltd Bengaluru

#### Summary

Experienced Recruiter with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Sourcing, Screening, IT Recruitment, Recruiting, and Technical Recruiting. Strong human resources professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused in Electronics and Communications Engineering from Gandhi Institute of Technology And Management (GITAM), Bhubaneswar.

### Experience

Microsoft Technical Recruiter February 2020 - Present (7 months) Bengaluru Area, India

# Capgemini Technical Recruiter

July 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Maintec Technologies Inc. HR Recruiter May 2016 - July 2018 (2 years 3 months)

### Education

Gandhi Institute of Technology And Management (GITAM), Bhubaneswar Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2009 - 2013)